Most competitive guy you're ever going
to mean, again, as as hard of a coach as
I ever wanted to try to be on him, I was
never going to be harder on him than he
is on himself, and that's you know,
that's the joy of coaching guys like
Caleb with that just know they're
pushing themselves so hard. So, as a
coach, all you want to do is give them
as much information as you can so they
can go do everything that they do so so
well.
Caleb, how difficult has this process
been? You're trying to put your best
foot forward for teams, and in the
meantime, you can't work out the way you
want to and those kinds of things. Uh I
mean, it's out of my hands at the end of
the day. Uh I've played 44 games of
film. I did my stuff out here, and
at the end of the day, it's in their
ball's in their court kind of right now,
so uh I'm just chilling. Just just
working and continuing to work on my
game. Now, what did you think of today?
I mean, you put a lot of stuff on film
at the combine, but what do you think
about today? Uh I thought I did did
really smooth, did the drizzly well,
caught the ball well.
Uh showed a little range.
I did my stuff. Yeah. I think one of the
things, too, you see is just, you know,
his ability to track the ball in the
deep part of the field, and his
athleticism and how smooth he is going
up in the air to get the ball. One of
the things you forget about Caleb, he's
also probably the best punt returner
that's going to be out there, too. So,
his ability to impact the game in those
ways and what he can do when the ball's
in his hands. So, it's good to see him,
you know, go out, move, flip his hips,
playing the deep part. Um certainly, we
know how great and effective he is at
the line of scrimmage and playing down
in the box and his instincts and all
that stuff, but the deep field play is
great. Question for both of you guys. We
We haven't seen many [snorts] safeties
go in the top 10 in the NFL draft. I
think four since 2000. What What do you
What do you both make of that, and then
why is he maybe different in that he's
going to potentially go top Yeah, I
mean, I'm going to just say the same
thing I said at the combine. At the end
of the day, it's about affecting the
game. Whoever affects the games, that's
who needs to be picked the highest, and
I feel like I do it at at the highest
level, so
that's really all I have to say about
that. Yeah, I think one of the things,
you know, look, when you draft in the
NFL, you're always looking to, all
right, who scores touchdowns, right, and
who prevents touchdowns in coverage,
pass rush on defense.
Um but then on top of that, okay, who's
the face of your franchise? Like, who
are you bringing in that's going to
represent your ownership, your
organization, everything that you want
to embody as a as a team. And uh when
you got guys that are a racer-type
players in the defense that can play in
the multiple different roles, that can
be in the middle, be outside, be in the
box, be in the deep part of the field,
uh those guys are going to be on your
your team, your organization for 15-plus
years, you take them whenever you can
get them, and that's, you know, that's
Caleb. Yeah.